(Howard:)Okay, now you're just being unrealistic.
Anyway, that movie was 20 years ago.
(Howard:)Imagine how saggy
those things would be.
You're gonna throw away a great girl
like Bernadette...
(Penny:)...because you're holding out
for some fantasy?
(Howard:)Hey, just because you settled
doesn't mean I have to.
(Leonard:)Excuse me, I'm sitting here.
(Penny:)Hey, I did not settle for Leonard.
(Penny:)I mean, obviously, he isn't
the kind of guy I usually go out with.
(Penny:)You know, physically.
(Leonard:)Again, I'm right here.
(Penny:)I do not judge a book by its cover.
I am interested in the person underneath.
I am here, right? You see me?
(Howard:)Hey, I'm interested
in what's inside people too.
But, you know, why is it wrong
to want those insides wrapped up...
(Howard:)...in, say, the delicious caramel
that is Halle Berry?